uras Singh was one of the most
successful allrounder cricketer in the
world he can ball he can bat he can
field as well in the same way when it
comes to the world of investment if you
want to take a good diversification
across the asset class including Equity
debt gold and ETFs well definitely you
should invest into multi-asset mutual
fund Hello friends this is Vijay and
welcome back to my Channel friends in
this video I would like to discuss about
one multi-asset mutual fund which is ICC
presential multi-asset Mutual Fund
multi-asset mutual fund is nothing but a
it will invest across the asset class
including Equity debt gold and ETFs so
that we'll get a good diversification
fund which is started in 2002 it's been
21 years now since insertion the fund
has been a biggest wealth creator for
many investor friends today I would like
to discuss more about this fund friends
you can stay till the end because you'll
be learning a lot in this video let's
get started ICC provential multi-asset
mutual fund which was launched in 2002
it's been 21 years now if you look at
the a asset under management which is
25,000 CR if you look at the expense
ratio which is 1% if you look at the nav
net asset value which is 600 if you look
at the asset allocation 65% of
allocation into Equity Market 35% of
allocation into gold debt and edfs
within Equity 48% of allocation into
large cap 8% of allocation into midcap
2% of allocation into small cap if you
look at the top five sectors 12% of
allocation into banking 7% of allocation
into Power 6% of allocation into PHA and
biotechnology 5% of allocation into
automobile 4.5% of allocation into it if
you look at the top 10 stocks the first
one is ntpc National thermal power
Corporation IC Bank HDFC Bank BH AEL
maruti Suzuki OMC Reliance industry
enosis Sun Pharma ICI Lombard General
Insurance if you look at the return
since Inception the fund has generated
20% of return which is very good 10,000
rupees sip in the scheme since
insception now your investment value
will be 25 lakh market value will be 3
CR rupees this is how this scheme has
created huge wealth for many investors
friends once you invest into the
multi-asset mutual fund you'll be
getting a good diversification across
the asset class including Equity debt
gold and ETFs so that you can create a
balanced portfolio along with that if
you're too much worried about the market
volatility Market ups and downs
investing into the multi asset mutual
fund is one of the best option as it is
having a good exposure in debt and cold
so that you can reduce your risk friends
I hope you find this video useful if you
like this video please to subscribe
please share it with your community if
you required any help with regards to
mutual fund you can contact me in the
below link thank you thank you so much